Guide to the Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Archive 1949 - 2011 MSS.326
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Flaherty Film Seminars
  - Subseries A: Audio Recordings
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 7, 1991; ID: 326.0506 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0506)
      "I Need Your Full Cooperation" "Interpretation of Dreams" Moderator: Patty Zimmerman Guests: Andrei Zagdansky, Kathy High
      "I Need Your Full Cooperation: "Interpretation of Dreams" Moderator: Patty Zimmerman Guests: Andrei Zagdansky, Kathy High
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 7, 1991; ID: 326.0507 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0507)
      Original Number: 1991-11
      "Plastic Jesus" Moderator: Erik Barnouw Guests: Lazar Stojanovic
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 8, 1991; ID: 326.0508 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0508)
      Original Number: 1991-12
      "Canticle of Stones" Moderator: Viola Shatik Guests: Ella Shohat, Viola Shatik
      "Intifada: The Introduction to An End of An Argument" "Speaking for Oneself-Sepaking for Others" Moderator: Viola Shatik Guests: Ella Shohat
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, 1991; ID: 326.0509 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0509)
      Original Number: 1991-13
      "Measure of Distance" Elia Suleiman
      "Symbiophychotaxiplasm: Take One" William Greaves Jakkie
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 8, 1991; ID: 326.0510 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0510)
      Original Number: 1991-14
      William Greaves "Symbiopychotaxiplasm:Take One" Moderator: Jackie
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 9, 1991; ID: 326.0511 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0511)
      Original Number: 1991-15
      "Pay Any Means Necessary" "Mysteries of July" Moderator: Patty Zimmerman, Richard Horskowitz
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 8, 1992; ID: 326.0512 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0512, Box Shared Fales 134, Cd 326.0512)
      Original Number: 1992-01
      Opening: Tom Johson "Brother's Keeper" Joe Berlinger
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 9, 1992; ID: 326.0513 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0513)
      Original Number: 1992-02
      "Bullets for Breakfast" Molly Fisher
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 9, 1992; ID: 326.0514 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0514)
      Original Number: 1992-03
      Intro: Scott MacDonald Dis. Reggio & Porter
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 10, 1992; ID: 326.0515 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0515)
      Original Number: 1992-04
      Scott MacDonald Ken Jacobs
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 10, 1992; ID: 326.0516 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0516)
      Original Number: 1992-05
      Wille Verella/Chris Wellsby Cheryl Dunye
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 10, 1992; ID: 326.0517 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0517)
      Original Number: 1992-06
      "Vinh" Keiko Tsuno
      Cheryl Dunye
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 11, 1992; ID: 326.0518 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0518)
      Original Number: 1992-07
      "Emperor's Naked Army" Interview with Kazuo Hara
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 11, 1992; ID: 326.0519 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0519)
      Original Number: 1992-08
      interview with Keiko Tsuno "Vinh"
      Interview with Kazuo Hara "Emperor's Naked Army"
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 11, 1992; ID: 326.0520 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0520)
      Original Number: 1992-09
      Tom Johnson intro to "Brother's Keeper"
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 12, 1992; ID: 326.0521 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0521)
      Original Number: 1992-10
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 12, 1992; ID: 326.0522 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0522)
      Original Number: 1992-11
      Portia Cobb
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, 1992; ID: 326.0523 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0523)
      Original Number: 1992-12
      Portia Cobb/Willie
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 13, 1992; ID: 326.0524 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0524)
      Original Number: 1992-13
      Willie
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 13, 1992; ID: 326.0525 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0525)
      Original Number: 1992-14
      Ed Radtke & Jeff Wray
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 13, 1992; ID: 326.0526 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0526)
      Original Number: 1992-15
      Camille Billops & James Hatch
      Camille Billops & James Hatch/Willie
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 14, 1992; ID: 326.0527 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0527, Box Shared Fales 134, Cd 326.0527)
      Original Number: 1992-16
      Wrap-up
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 7, 1993; ID: 326.0528 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0528)
      Original Number: 1993-01
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 8, 1993; ID: 326.0529 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0529)
      Original Number: 1993-02
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 8, 1993; ID: 326.0530 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0530, Box Shared Fales 134, Cd 326.0530)
      Original Number: 1993-03
      Leighton Pierce et. al
      Juan Downey Meena
      Access CD available
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 8, 1993; ID: 326.0531 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0531)
      Original Number: 1993-04
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 8, 1993; ID: 326.0532 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0532)
      Original Number: 1993-05
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 9, 1993; ID: 326.0533 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0533)
      Original Number: 1993-06
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 9, 1993; ID: 326.0534 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0534)
      Original Number: 1993-07
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 9, 1993; ID: 326.0535 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0535)
      Original Number: 1993-08
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 9, 1993; ID: 326.0536 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0536)
      Original Number: 1993-09
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 10, 1993; ID: 326.0537 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0537)
      Original Number: 1993-10
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 10, 1993; ID: 326.0538 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0538)
      Original Number: 1993-11
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 10, 1993; ID: 326.0539 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0539)
      Original Number: 1993-12
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 11, 1993; ID: 326.0540 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0540)
      Original Number: 1993-13
      Moderator: Margarita de la Vega Hurtado
      Kidnapping of Sylia Motta, daughter of Bogota industrialist [Panal/carway] by filmmaker/sisiter of kidnapped victim and cinematogrpaher
      filmmaker Camila Hotta
      Access CD available. Ask for parts 1 and 2.
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 11, 1993; ID: 326.0541 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0541)
      Original Number: 1993-14
      Marta Rodriguez with Margarita de la Vega Hurtado & Christopher Ortiz
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 11, 1993; ID: 326.0542 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0542)
      Original Number: 1993-15
      John Akomfrah with June Givani
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 12, 1993; ID: 326.0543 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0543)
      Original Number: 1993-16
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 12, 1993; ID: 326.0544 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0544)
      Original Number: 1993-17
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 12, 1993; ID: 326.0545 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0545)
      Original Number: 1993-18
      Discussion wrap-up
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, 1993; ID: 326.0546 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0546)
      Original Number: 1993-19
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, August 13, 1993; ID: 326.0547 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0547)
      Original Number: 1993-20
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 21, 1993; ID: 326.0548 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0548, Box Shared Fales 134, Cd 326.0548)
      Original Number: 1993-21
      Juan Downey
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 6, 1994; ID: 326.0549 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0549)
      Original Number: 1994-01
      Saturday Night Intros
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 7, 1994; ID: 326.0550 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0550)
      Original Number: 1994-02
      Contents unknown.
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 7, 1994; ID: 326.0551 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0551)
      Original Number: 1994-03
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 7, 1994; ID: 326.0552 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0552)
      Original Number: 1994-04
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, 1994; ID: 326.0553 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0553)
      Original Number: 1994-05
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 8, 1994; ID: 326.0554 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0554)
      Original Number: 1994-06
      Nick Deo Campo
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, 1994; ID: 326.0555 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0555)
      Original Number: 1994-07
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, 1994; ID: 326.0556 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0556)
      Original Number: 1994-08
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, 1994; ID: 326.0557 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0557)
      Original Number: 1994-09
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 1994; ID: 326.0558 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0558)
      Original Number: 1994-10
      Uski Roti
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, 1994; ID: 326.0559 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0559)
      Original Number: 1994-11
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, 1994; ID: 326.0560 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0560)
      Original Number: 1994-12
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 10, 1994; ID: 326.0561 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0561)
      Original Number: 1994-13
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 10, 1994; ID: 326.0562 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0562)
      Original Number: 1994-14
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 11, 1994; ID: 326.0563 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0563)
      Original Number: 1994-15
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 11, 1994; ID: 326.0564 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0564)
      Original Number: 1994-16
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, 1994; ID: 326.0565 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0565)
      Original Number: 1994-17
      Dhrupad
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 11, 1994; August 12, 1994; ID: 326.0566 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0566)
      Original Number: 1994-18
      Siddeshwari
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, 1996; ID: 326.0567 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0567)
      Original Number: 1996-01
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, 1996; ID: 326.0568 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0568)
      Original Number: 1996-02
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, 1996; ID: 326.0569 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0569)
      Original Number: 1996-03
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, 1996; ID: 326.0570 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0570)
      Original Number: 1996-04
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 4, 1996; ID: 326.0571 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0571)
      Original Number: 1996-05
      Dratfield Brunch
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 6, 1996; ID: 326.0572 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0572)
      Original Number: 1996-06
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, 1996; ID: 326.0573 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0573)
      Original Number: 1996-07
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, 1996; ID: 326.0574 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0574)
      Original Number: 1996-08
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, 1996; ID: 326.0575 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0575)
      Original Number: 1996-09
      Kuchar/Vasulka
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 1996; ID: 326.0576 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0576)
      Original Number: 1996-10
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 1996; ID: 326.0577 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0577)
      Original Number: 1996-11
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August, 1996; ID: 326.0578 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0578)
      Original Number: 1996-12
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August, 1996; ID: 326.0579 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0579)
      Original Number: 1996-13
      Contents Unknown.
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 7, 1996; August 8, 1996; ID: 326.0580 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0580)
      Original Number: 1996-14
      Merata Blessing
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 8, 1996; ID: 326.0581 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0581)
      Original Number: 1996-15
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 01, August 7, 1998; ID: 326.0582 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0582)
      Original Number: 1999-01
      Wachsmann and Rosenblatt
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 7, 1998; ID: 326.0583 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0583)
      Original Number: 1998-01
      Wachsman, Rosenblatt/Mandel
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 8, 1998; ID: 326.0584 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0584)
      Original Number: 1998-02
      Peter Forgacs A.M. Session
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 8, 1998; ID: 326.0585 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0585)
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 8, 1998; ID: 326.0586 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0586)
      Original Number: 1998-03
      McLean and Marcovich afternoon session
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 8, 1998; ID: 326.0587 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0587)
      Sienna McLean and Carlos Marcovich Afternoon
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 8, 1998; ID: 326.0588 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0588)
      Original Number: 1998-04
      Ning Ying
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 8, 1998; ID: 326.0589 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0589)
      Ning Ying P.M. Discussion
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0590 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0590)
      Original Number: 1998-05
      Hillel Tryster
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0591 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0591)
      Hillel Tryster (Spielberg Archive)
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0592 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0592)
      Hillel Tryster (duplicate)
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0593 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0593)
      Original Number: 1998-06
      Kore-Eda Hirokazu Afternoon
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0594 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0594)
      Kore-Eda
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0595 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0595)
      Original Number: 1998-07
      Peter Forgacs night session
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0596 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0596)
      Peter Forgacs
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 10, 1998; ID: 326.0597 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0597)
      Original Number: 1998-08
      Ning Ying morning
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 10, 1998; ID: 326.0598 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0598)
      Original Number: 1998-09
      Afternoon [Contents Unknown]
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 10, 1998; ID: 326.0599 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0599)
      Monday afternoon, Forgas
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 10, 1998; ID: 326.0600 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0600)
      Original Number: 1998-10
      Kore-eda Hirozaku - Evening
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 11, 1998; ID: 326.0601 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0601)
      Original Number: 1998-11
      Rosenblatt/ Friedrich tape one
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 11, 1998; ID: 326.0602 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0602)
      Original Number: 1998-12
      Rosenblatt / Friedrich tape two
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, 1998; ID: 326.0603 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0603)
      Original Number: 1998-13
      Ilan Ziv and Daoud Kuttab
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, [undated]; ID: 326.0604 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0604)
      Original Number: 1998-14
      Kore Eda
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 12, 1998; ID: 326.0605 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0605)
      Original Number: 1998-15
      Loni Ding - Afternoon session,
      Moderator: Barbara Abrash
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 12, 1998; ID: 326.0606 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0606)
      Original Number: 1998-16
      W. Raad and P. Forgacs - Evening
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 13, 1998; ID: 326.0607 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0607)
      Original Number: 1998-17
      Flaherty Closing Discussion
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 13, 1998; ID: 326.0608 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0608)
      Original Number: 1998-18
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, June 5, 1999; ID: 326.0609 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0609)
      Original Format: Panasonic DAT
      Intro remarks, Mississippi eyes, 6.5 morning session, Jason Livingston,
      Orlando Bagwell, Flaherty, Duke University
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 5, 1999; ID: 326.0610 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0610)
      Original Format: Sony DAT
      Original Number: 1999-02
      Moderator: Orlando Bagwell
      Jeanie Jordon, John Else, Group Introductions, recorded by Jack Farrish and Rob Koegler
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 5, 1999; ID: 326.0611 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0611)
      Original Number: 1999-03
      Opening Remarks: Orlando Bagwell "Four Little Girls" Jackie
      Discussion Moderator: Sam Pollard
      Recorded by Jack Parrish and Rob Koegler
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, June 5, 1999; ID: 326.0612 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0612)
      Original Number: 1999-04
      Intro Remarks, Richard Herskowitz, Peleshian: The End, Inhabitants Our City,
      T with discussion, Translator: Boris
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 6, 1999; ID: 326.0613 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0613)
      Original Number: 1999-05
      Flaherty, Duke University
      Intro Remarks: Richard Herskowitz, Louisiana Story, Study Film, Richard "Ricky" Leacook,
      and Discussion moderatred by R. Herskowitz
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, June 6, 1999; ID: 326.0614 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0614)
      Original Number: 1999-06
      Flaherty, Duke University Afternoon Intro Remarks R. Herskowitz David Simpson and Discussion with David Simpson
      Moderated by R. Herskowtiz
      Noblessa Oblige Halstend St
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, June 7, 1999; ID: 326.0615 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0615)
      Original Number: 1999-07
      Evening session, Intro Remarks, Herskowitz, Van der Keuken Global Village, Discussion Johann Van der Keuken, Moderator: Richard Herskowitz
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, June 7, 1999; ID: 326.0616 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0616)
      Original Number: 1999-08
      Morning: Ricky Leacock, Holga video, French TV sequence, clip from SIberian and discussion,
      Afternoon: Intro: Jane Gaines, Lucy Massie Phenix, Elizabeth Barrett, Stranger with a camera, and discussion with Lucy Phenix and Elizabeth Barrett, Moderator: Jane Gaines
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, June 7, 1999; ID: 326.0617 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0617)
      Original Number: 1999-09
      End of discussion with Elizabeth Barrett and Lucy Phenix moderated by Jane Gaines, Evening, Intro R. Herskowitz, David Williams
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 7, 1999; ID: 326.0618 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0618)
      Original Number: 1999-10
      Filmmaker: David Williams, Moderator: Recording: Rob Koegler
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 8, 1999; ID: 326.0619 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0619)
      Original Number: 1999-11
      Intro Remarks: Orlando Bagwell, John Else, Cadillac Desert,
      Discussion: John Else, Moderator: Orlando Bagwell, Recording: Rob Koegler
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 8, 1999; ID: 326.0620 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0620)
      Original Number: 1999-12
      Evening Session: The first half of the opening remarks can be found on videotape, the second half of the opening remarks are here.
      Remarks by Mark McFaddin, Scott Stark, Tom Whiteside (Moderator), Rob Koegler (Recording), Jason (Recording)
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 9, 1999; ID: 326.0621 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0621)
      Original Number: 1999-13
      Morning Session, Intro remarks: Orlando Bagwell, Jackie Jones, Discussion: Same as above, Recording: Jack
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 9, 1999; ID: 326.0622 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0622)
      Original Number: 1999-14
      Afternoon Session, Phillip Mallory Jones, Catherine Milton
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 8, 1999; ID: 326.0623 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0623)
      Original Number: 1999-15
      Afternoon Session, Intro Remarks: R. Herskowtiz, Jennifer and Kevin McCoy
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, June 9, 1999; ID: 326.0624 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0624)
      Original Number: 1999-16
      Evening Session: Intro: R. Herskowitz, Caspar Straacke, Discussion: Laura Marks (Moderator), Caspar Straacke (Discussion)
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, June 10, 1999; ID: 326.0625 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0625)
      Original Number: 1999-17
      Morning Session: Intro: Orlando Bagwell, Discussion: John Else, Johann van der Keuken, Final Evaluation Session
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, 2000; ID: 326.0626 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0626)
      Original Number: 2000-01
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 17, 2000; ID: 326.0627 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0627)
      Original Number: 2000-02
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 17, 2000; ID: 326.0628 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0628)
      Original Number: 2000-03
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, June 17, 2000; ID: 326.0629 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0629)
      Original Number: 2000-04
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 18, 2000; ID: 326.0630 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0630)
      Original Number: 2000-05
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, June 18, 2000; ID: 326.0631 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0631)
      Original Number: 2000-06
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, June 19, 2000; ID: 326.0632 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0632)
      Original Number: 2000-07
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, June 19, 2000; ID: 326.0633 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0633)
      Original Number: 2000-08
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, June 19, 2000; ID: 326.0634 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0634)
      Original Number: 2000-09
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 20, 2000; ID: 326.0635 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0635)
      Original Number: 2000-10
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 20, 2000; ID: 326.0636 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0636)
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 21, 2000; ID: 326.0638 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0638)
      Party
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, June 21, 2000; ID: 326.0637 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0637)
      Unknown contents.
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, June 22, 2000; ID: 326.0639 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0639)
    - 46th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 22, 2000; ID: 326.0640 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0640)
      Coz
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, June 15, 2001; ID: 326.0641 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0641)
      Original Number: 2001-01
      Films: Trut, Herman Slobbe, Beauty Will Change the World (excerpt),
      Guests: Heddy Honigmann, Carl Svenstedt
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 16, 2001; ID: 326.0642 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0642)
      Original Number: 2001-02
      Jo Anne Birnie Danzker, Photo slide show of Flaherty
    - 47th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 16, 2001; ID: 326.0643 (Box 14, Media ID: 326.0643)
      Original Number: 2001-03
      Robert Flaherty Photographs/Slide Show,